HAMZA IQBAL

Multan, Pakistan • +92-307-6966889 • iqbal.66889@gamil.com

SUMMARY

A Certified Google Search and Display Ads Specialist with an multi niche experience in Lead Generation SMM, SEM with innovative marketing campaigns. As a Marketing Specialist, I am interested in finding a position where I can look to enhance my knowledge in internet marketing while setting the company apart and bringing the brand one step further.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Marketing Specialist, Propertyana Real Estate - Dubai

Sep 2023 - Marr2024

- Multi Niche Leads Generation
- Keyword Research / Analysis
- Google Search Ads

- Meta Ads
- Landing Page Design
- SEO/SMM/SEM

Marketing Analyst, Redspider.ae - Multan Office/Remote

Feb2021 - Jul 2022

Sep 2019 - Jul 2023

- · Business Intelligence
- Data Analytics
- · Social Media Management

- Sales Insights
- · Content Creation

EDUCATION

BS in Computer Science - Namal University Mianwali, Pakistan Major Courses

Artificial Intelligence

Machine Learning

OOP

- Management
- Cryptography
- Software Engineering

CERTIFICATIONS

- Google Search Ads Certification
- Google Display Ads Certification
- Google Advanced Data Analytics Certification
- Google UX Certification

EXPERTISE

- GA4
- GTM
- · Meta Business Suite
- Meta Ads Manager

- Pandas
- WordPress
- ClickFunnels

HOBBIES

- Watching Football
- Reading Philosophy
- · Practice Stoicism
- International Politics